Guide to the Images of Yale Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Alphabetical List of Individuals, Series I
  - Wood, Oren M. (Box 75, Folder 2771)
  - Wood, William B. (Box 75, Folder 2772)
  - Wood, William Curtis (Box 75, Folder 2772)
  - Woodbine, Professor (Box 75, Folder 2772)
  - Woodbridge, Dudley (Box 75, Folder 2773)
  - Woodbridge, William Channing (Box 75, Folder 2773)
  - Woodbridge, William Reed (Box 75, Folder 2773)
  - Woodcock, Harold F. (Box 75, Folder 2774)
  - Woodfort, Stewart Lyndon (Box 75, Folder 2774)
  - Woodhall, George L. (Box 75, Folder 2774)
  - Woodman, Francis Joseph (Box 75, Folder 2775)
  - Woodruff, Asa A. (Box 75, Folder 2775)
  - Woodruff, Charles Hornblower (Box 75, Folder 2775)
  - Woodruff, Francis Eben (Box 75, Folder 2776)
  - Woodruff, George Washington (Box 75, Folder 2776)
  - Woodruff, George William Lane (Box 75, Folder 2776)
  - Woodruff, Henry Collins (Box 75, Folder 2777)
  - Woodruff, James H. (Box 75, Folder 2777)
  - Woodruff, L. Loss [Lorande Loss] (Box 75, Folder 2777)
  - Woodruff, R. K. (Box 75, Folder 2778)
  - Woodruff, Timothy Lester (Box 75, Folder 2778)
  - Woods, William Burnham (Box 75, Folder 2778)
  - Woodward, Asa B. (Box 75, Folder 2779)
  - Woodward, Elizabeth Cutler (Box 75, Folder 2779)
  - Woodward, John Butler (Box 75, Folder 2779)
  - Woodward, Stanley Trott (Box 75, Folder 2780)
  - Woodward, William Herrick (Box 75, Folder 2780)
  - Woody, Charles K., Jr. (Box 75, Folder 2780)
  - Wooller, Evan S. (Box 75, Folder 2781)
  - Woolley, Monte (Box 75, Folder 2781)
  - Woolner, Alfred Charles (Box 75, Folder 2781)
  - Woolsey, Benjamin (Box 75, Folder 2781)
  - Woolsey, John Munro (Box 75, Folder 2782)
  - Woolsey, Theodore Dwight (Box 75, Folder 2782)
    - Engravings (Box 75, Folder 2783)
    - Engravings with Jeremiah Day & Benjamin Silliman (Box 75, Folder 2784)
    - Photos, engravings, & negative (Box 75, Folder 2785-88)
    - Photos of statue (Box 75, Folder 2789)
    - Photos of grave in Grove. St. Cemetery (Box 75, Folder 2790)
  - Woolsey, Theodore Salisbury (Y. 1872) (Box 75, Folder 2791)
  - Woolsey, Theodore Salisbury (Y. 1901) (Box 75, Folder 2791)
  - Wooster, David (Box 75, Folder 2791)
  - Wooten, Sidney C. (Box 76, Folder 2792)
  - Worcester, Edwin Dean (Box 76, Folder 2792)
  - Worcester, Joseph Emerson (Box 76, Folder 2792)
  - Wordin, Nathaniel Eugene (Box 76, Folder 2793)
  - Worrall, J. Hunter (Box 76, Folder 2793)
  - Worrall, Walter Laning (Box 76, Folder 2793)
  - Worrall, Thaddeus T. (Box 76, Folder 2794)
  - Worthington, Harold (Box 76, Folder 2794)
  - Worthington, Lewis Sedam (Box 76, Folder 2794)
  - Wright, (Economics) (Box 76, Folder 2795)
  - Wright, Alexander H. (Box 76, Folder 2795)
  - Wright, Arthur Williams (Box 76, Folder 2796-97)
  - Wright, Charles A. (Box 76, Folder 2798)
  - Wright, Edward Augustus (Box 76, Folder 2798)
  - Wright, Edwin (Box 76, Folder 2798)
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd (Box 76, Folder 2799)
  - Wright, Fred Norman (Box 76, Folder 2800)
  - Wright, Hamilton (Box 76, Folder 2800)
  - Wright, Henry Burt (Box 76, Folder 2800)
  - Wright, Henry Parks (Box 76, Folder 2801-03)
  - Wright, Henry W. (Box 76, Folder 2804)
  - Wright, John R. (Box 76, Folder 2804)
  - Wright, Luther (Box 76, Folder 2804)
  - Wright, Orville (Box 77, Folder 2805)
  - Wright, Paul Darling (Box 77, Folder 2805)
  - Wright, William Runk (Box 77, Folder 2805)
  - Wright, William W. (Box 77, Folder 2806)
  - Wurts, Albert Smith (Box 77, Folder 2806)
  - Wurts, Charles Pemberton (Box 77, Folder 2807)
  - Wurts, John (Box 77, Folder 2807)
  - Wurts, Pierre Jay (Box 77, Folder 2807)
  - Wyers, Frederick Augustus (Box 77, Folder 2808)
  - Wyllys, George (Box 77, Folder 2808)
  - Wyman, William Cutler (Box 77, Folder 2808)
  - Wynkoop, Theodore (Box 77, Folder 2809)
  - Wyre, Duke (Box 77, Folder 2809)
  - Yale, David Lewis (Box 77, Folder 2809)
  - Yale, Elihu (See also: Oversive) (Box 77, Folder 2810-11)
  - Yale, James Elihu Ivor (Box 77, Folder 2812)
  - Yale, Elisha (Box 77, Folder 2813)
  - Yamakawa, Kenjiro (Box 77, Folder 2813)
  - Yarbrough, R. Clyde (Box 77, Folder 2813)
  - Yard, John (Box 77, Folder 2814)
  - Yardley, Henry Albert (Box 77, Folder 2814)
  - Yates, Horatio Green (Box 77, Folder 2814)
  - Yates, Walter R. (Box 77, Folder 2815)
  - Yeager, Orson Ellsworth, Jr. (Box 77, Folder 2815)
  - Yeatman, Thomas (Box 77, Folder 2815)
  - Yergason, Henry B. B. (Box 77, Folder 2816)
  - Yerkes, Robert M. (Box 77, Folder 2816)
  - Yeu, Fun Tan (Box 77, Folder 2816)
  - Yew, Chung Mun (Box 77, Folder 2817)
  - York, Allan W. (Box 77, Folder 2818)
  - York, Edward H. (Box 77, Folder 2818)
  - York, Lewis E. (Box 77, Folder 2818)
  - York, Samuel A. (Box 77, Folder 2819)
  - York, William L. (Box 77, Folder 2819)
  - Young, Ezra Hallock (Box 77, Folder 2819)
  - Young, Herbert Stanley (Box 77, Folder 2820)
  - Young, John Wallace (Box 77, Folder 2820)
  - Young, Karl (Box 77, Folder 2820)
  - Young, Mason (Box 77, Folder 2821)
  - Young, Robert (Box 77, Folder 2821)
  - Young, Thomas (Box 77, Folder 2821)
  - Yule, George Gordon (Box 77, Folder 2822)
  - Yundt, Edwin Henry (Box 77, Folder 2823)
  - Zacher, Edmund (Box 77, Folder 2823)
  - Zegans, Leonard (Box 77, Folder 2823)
  - Zeleny, John (Box 77, Folder 2824)
  - Zellner, Richard (Box 77, Folder 2824)
  - Ziegler, Harry D. (Box 77, Folder 2824)
  - Zon, Raphael (Box 77, Folder 2825)
  - Zorthian, Jirayr H. (Box 77, Folder 2825)
  - Zummalt, E. V. (Box 77, Folder 2825)
  - Unidentified Pictures (Box 78, Folder 2826-2833)
  - Unidentified Pictures (Box 79, Folder 2834-2836)
  - Unaffiliated Individuals (Yale Law School) (Box 79, Folder 2834-2836)
    - Allen, William (Box 80, Folder 2837)
    - Andrews, James (Box 80, Folder 2837)
    - Bayard, Samuel (Box 80, Folder 2837)
    - Benjamin, Judah Philip (Box 80, Folder 2837)
    - Bentham, Jeremy (Box 80, Folder 2838)
    - Blackstone, Sir William (Box 80, Folder 2838)
    - Brandeis, Louis Debitz (Box 80, Folder 2838)
    - Burton, Horace Hamon (Box 80, Folder 2839)
    - Campbell, John Campbell, First Baron (Box 80, Folder 2839)
    - Chase, Salmon Portland (Box 80, Folder 2839)
    - Coke, Sir Edward (Box 80, Folder 2839)
    - Day, William R. (Box 80, Folder 2840)
    - Eldon, Lord John Scott (Box 80, Folder 2840)
    - Fuller, Melville Weston (Box 80, Folder 2840)
    - Hall, F. B. (Box 80, Folder 2840)
    - Hewart, [Gordon, First Baron?] (Box 80, Folder 2841)
    - Holms, Oliver Wendell (Box 80, Folder 2841)
    - Hughes, Charles Evans (Box 80, Folder 2841)
    - Jay, John (Box 80, Folder 2841)
    - Lamor, F. R. (Box 80, Folder 2842)
    - Lugdon, Sir Edward Burtenshaw (Box 80, Folder 2842)
    - Lyndhurst, John Singleton Copley, Baron (Box 80, Folder 2842)
    - MacLean, William Jr. (Box 80, Folder 2842)
    - McKenna, Joseph (Box 80, Folder 2843)
    - McReynolds, J. C. (Box 80, Folder 2843)
    - Marshall, John (Box 80, Folder 2843)
    - Morgan, Edmund Morris (Box 80, Folder 2843)
    - Robertson, A. Heaton (Box 80, Folder 2844)
    - Rutledge, John (Box 80, Folder 2844)
    - Stowell, William Scott, Baron (Box 80, Folder 2844)
    - Seldon, John (Box 80, Folder 2844)
    - Stone, Horlan Fiske (Box 80, Folder 2845)
    - Swift, Zephaniah (Box 80, Folder 2845)
    - Taft, Henry W. (Box 80, Folder 2845)
    - Taney, Roger Brooke (Box 80, Folder 2845)
    - Thomas, Edwin S. (Box 80, Folder 2846)
    - Thurlow, Edward S. (Box 80, Folder 2846)
    - Wheeler, George Wakeman (Box 80, Folder 2846)
    - White, Edward Douglas (Box 80, Folder 2846)
    - Wickersham, George (Box 80, Folder 2846)
    - Unidentified Individuals (Box 80, Folder 2847)
- Oversize, Series II
  - Angell, James Rowland (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Arnold, George Waterman (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Brandeis, Louis D. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Brewer, Josiah David (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Brewer, Mr and Mrs. David J. (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Brewster, Kingman (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Butler, Pierce (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Bushnell, Samuel K. (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Calhoun, John Caldwell (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Bulkley, Jothathan O. (1923), circa 1918-1923 (Box 82, Folder 7-9)
  - Bush, George with Babe Ruth (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Cairns, Sir Hugh McCaumont (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Chatfield, Frederich Huntington, circa 1928 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Cleveland, Grover (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Cozens,Hartz Herbert H. (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Culter, Timothy (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Dana, James Dwight (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Deland, Lorin F. (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Darrow, Clarence (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Day, Jeremiah (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Devane, William (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Douglas, Wm. Orville (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Drummond, Henry (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Dwight, Timothy (Box 83, Folder 17-18)
  - Farr, Harlan (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Foch, Ferdinand (British Field Marshall), 1921 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    Scope and Contents
    Convocation procession on College Street in front of Woolsey Hall; pictured with Yale president James Rowland Angell and former president Arthur T. Hadley; signed by Foch, November 12, 1921
  - Griswold, A. Whitney (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Green, Gulliver Ashbel (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Hadley, Arthur (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Hale, Nathan Harstom (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Harriman, Edward Avery (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Healy, Thomas (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Johnson, Rev. Stephen (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Jones, T. A.D. (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Keith, Allen (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Kelly, Sir. Fitzroy (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Lampson, William (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Lapham, Henry (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Lane, Agnes Rose (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Longley, W.R. (Dean of Freshman 1937-1938) (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Lounsbury, Thomas Raynesford (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - Professors: S. Lynd, R. Cook, H. Beuda, J. LaPalombash (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - Mansfield, William Murray (Box 84, Folder 33)
  - Mitford, William (Box 84, Folder 33)
  - Meigs, Josiah (Box 84, Folder 34)
  - Morse, Samuel F.B. (Box 84, Folder 35)
  - Munroe, Elbert B. (Box 84, Folder 36)
  - Norton, John Pitkin (Box 84, Folder 37)
  - Peck, Tracy (Box 85, Folder 38)
  - Phelps, William Lyon (Box 85, Folder 39)
  - Pierson, Abraham (Box 85, Folder 40)
  - Porter, John A. (Box 85, Folder 41)
  - Porter, Noah (Box 85, Folder 42)
  - Quarles, Donald Aubrey (Box 85, Folder 43)
  - Rand, Paul (Box 85, Folder 44)
  - Record, Samuel J. (Dean) (Box 85, Folder 44)
  - Root, Eling (Box 85, Folder 45)
  - Sanford, Edward T. (Box 85, Folder 46)
  - Seymour, Charles (Box 85, Folder 47)
  - Silliman, Benjamin (Box 85, Folder 48)
  - Engraving of Jeremiah Day, Theodore Dwight Woolsey, and Benjamin Silliman on Commencement Day (see MADID # 764), 1860 July 26 (Box 85, Folder 85a)
  - Sinnot, Edmund W. (Box 85, Folder 48)
  - Sterling, John (Box 85, Folder 49)
  - Stern, Robert A. M. (Box 85, Folder 49)
  - Stiles, Ezra and Family (Box 85, Folder 50)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps (Box 86, Folder 51)
  - Stones, Harlan F. (Box 86, Folder 52)
  - Sutherland, George (Box 86, Folder 52)
  - Strong, William (Box 86, Folder 53)
  - Talmadge, Benjamin (Box 86, Folder 53)
  - Swan, Thomas Walter (Box 86, Folder 54)
  - Taft, Robert Alphonso (Box 86, Folder 54A)
  - Taft, William Howard (Box 86, Folder 55)
  - Toumey, James W. (Box 86, Folder 56)
  - Twitchell, T. A. (Box 86, Folder 57)
  - Van Devanter, Willis (Box 86, Folder 58)
  - White, E. D. (Box 86, Folder 58)
  - Willkie, Wendell (Box 86, Folder 59)
  - Williams, Rev. Nathan W. (Box 86, Folder 59)
  - Woodruff, Timothy L. (Box 86, Folder 60)
  - Woolsey, Theodore Dwight (Box 86, Folder 61)
  - Yale, Elihu (gravestone) (Box 86, Folder 62)
  - Yale, Elihu (portrait print-originally in a frame) (Box 86, Folder 62)
  - Unidentified (Box 86, Folder 63)
  - Slides and Transparencies
    - Albers, Josef (Box 87)
    - Brewster, Kingman inauguration (Box 88)
    - Brewster, Kingman inauguration (Box 89)
    - Griswold, A. Whitney funeral (Box 90)
    - Moore, Charles Willard (Box 91)
    - Tanis, Rev. (Box 92)
  - Folio
    - Alden, Roger (Box DR27F88)
    - Angier, Roswell Parker (Box DR27F88)
    - Arnold, Thurman Wesley, 1937 (Box DR14F45)
    - Baldwin, Roger S., Y 1811 (Box DR27F88)
    - Betts, Samuel R, Class of 1875 (Box DR27F88)
    - Brewer, Justice David (Box DR27F88)
    - Brewer, Louis Landon (Mrs. David Brewer) (Box DR27F88)
    - Brown, Joseph E, 1846 Law (Box DR14F44)
    - Calhoun, John C., circa 1849 (Box DR28F89)
    - Caner, Rev. Henry (Box DR27F88)
    - Cardozo, Benjamin, 1920-1921 (Box DR14F45)
    - Choate, Joseph 1901 Law (Hon) (Box DR14F44)
    - Day, George Edward (Box DR13F39)
    - Day, Mrs. George Edward (Box DR13F39)
    - Dwight, Timothy (elder) (Box DR1F2)
    - Dwight, Timohty (younger) (Box DR1F2)
    - Evarts, William M., Class of 1837 (Box DR28F89)
    - Farr, Hollon A. (Box DR28F89)
    - Field, Daniel D. (with sons) (Box DR28F89)
    - Foche, Marechal, 1919 (Box DR28F89)
    - French, Robert Dudley (Box DR28F89)
    - Fuller, Melville W. 1901 Law (Box DR28F89)
    - Fuller, Melville W. 1901 Law (Box DR14F44)
    - Giamatti, A. Bartlett (painting) (Box DR1F2)
    - Goselin, Ens. Edward Webb (Box DR28F90)
    - Hale, Nathan (statue) (Box DR28F90)
    - Philip, 1st Earl of Hardwick (Box DR28F90)
    - Jones, F.S. (Box DR3F11)
    - Karrick, David B., Class of 1914 (Box DR28F90)
    - Kent, James, Class of 1781 (Box DR28F90)
    - Lohman, Carl (Box DR1F3)
    - Moseley, James A. (Box DR28F90)
    - Perkins, Edward C., Class of 1898 (Box DR28F91)
    - Phelps, William Lyon (Box DR28F91)
    - Porter, Noah (Box DR1F2)
    - Root, Elihu (Box DR14F45)
    - Sanford, Judge Edward J. (Box DR28F91)
    - Silliman, Benjamin (Box DR28F91)
    - Smyth, W.W. (Box DR28F91)
    - Stimpson, Henry (Box DR28F91)
    - Lord Strathcona (Box DR28F91)
    - Strong, William, Class of 1832 (Box DR28F91)
    - Taft, William Howard (Box DR14F45)
    - Taft, William Howard (6 photos), circa 1909-1911 (Box DR29F92)
    - Tallmadge, Benjamin (Box DR29F92)
    - Walden, Percy Talbot (Box DR13F37)
    - Wardlan, Ralph (Box DR29F93)
    - Welles, N.P. (Box DR29F93)
    - Wolfers, Arnold (Box DR29F93)
    - Woods, Hon. William B., Class of 1845 (Box DR29F93)
    - Wright, Henry P. (Box DR3F11)
  - Unaffiliated individuals (Law School)
    - Dole Sanford B. (Box DR14F46)
    - Marshall, John (Box DR14F46)
    - Moore, James Bassett (Box DR14F46)
    - Stowell, William Lord (Box DR14F46)
    - Webster, Daniel (Box DR14F46)
    - White, Edward Douglas (Box DR14F46)
  - Connecticut Supreme Court of Errors, 1904 (Box DR14F46)
  - US Supreme Court
    - 1789-1909 (Box DR14F46)
    - Chief Justices, 1801-1921 (Box DR14F46)
      - circa 1882 (Box DR14F46)
      - circa 1890s (Box DR14F46)
      - circa 1905 (Box DR14F46)
- Photographs of Yale faculty, staff, and students, Accession 1993-A-034
  - Photographs of Yale faculty, staff, and students, circa 1846-1871 (Box 1–2)
- Poster and program, Accession 2007-A-072
  - Poster with pictures of retired police officers and retirement dinner program, 2001 (Box 1)
- Sketch of George Lincoln Hendrickson, Circa 1942-1948; Accession 2015-A-056
  - Pencil sketch of George Lincoln Hendrickson by Mimi Jennewein von Pritzelwitz van der Horst, Circa 1942-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)